Good morning, Fujimoto!
Good morning!
You know how early it is, right?
Yeah!
You're going to be like this every day, aren't you. What do you want today?
I want to help out!
Please, let me help you!
Oh man. C'mon, you can't--
Oh!
Good morning, Kobato and Fujimoto.
Good morning!
Are you helping him out again today?
Yeah!
It must be so nice to have her around, Fujimoto.
Quit joking around.
Why is it so important to help me?
Don't let your guard down, Kobato.
Take your eyes off him for a second and I'm sure he'll hurt himself again.
Of course!
What shall I do?
Even the obvious things are always so hard
I just want to grin when I'm happy, sing when I'm in love
They say my dreams will come true someday
but when will someday come? I can't wait!
Count one, two, three and spread my arms
Gather the light to myself
Where is it? Tell me what I can do
Even if I'm hurt so much, even if I run so hard
Even if I collapse crying over and over, I still
believe in my amazing future
Every day.
I'll do it myself!
Oh, by the way!
I found this, let me pin it up for you!
Don't just go and--
What else shall I do?
... Kobato's Wish
Where are you going today?
Yesterday was the library, and the day before college.
Work.
I thought you had the day off.
How many times have I told you?
If you're just--
It's not pity or self-sacrifice.
I told you, stop bothering me.
Do you go for walks, Fujimoto?
Walks are great fun!
You're the only one who has that much fun with them.
Let's go somewhere fun!
Hey!
Yeah, they went out together.
Right.
It's just a matter of time.
It's like that for everyone.
Even you two.
What do you want, anyway?
What?
You've been all scrunched up here.
So I wanted you to have some fun.
See, there's boats!
Let's ride one!
Wait, a boat?
Hey!
I think it costs money, though...
Oh man.
Hey.
You're gonna hit something.
Let me at it.
No! You're hurt!
If you werry about that, we're never going to make it back!
Never make it back...
I'll try my best!
I'll get us there!
Don't dip the oar that deep.
Okay.
Use your legs, too.
Sure!
Heave-ho!
We're moving!
This is great!
Such an optimist.
Fujimoto?
You've gotten a little better up here.
What are you up to?
I'm trying to cheer Fujimoto up. Next we're going to feed the fishies!
That's not what I meant! Don't you understand the mess you're in!?
Yeah! I spent more money on Fujimoto...
But at least I got change!
That's not it! What do you even thing I'm talking about!? You're out of time!
Yeah!
That's why I'm trying my best!
I've got to hurry back!
Come on! I'm not done talking to you!
Here, fishie, fishie! Dinnertime!
Where are you?
Why don't you try, Fujimoto?
Leave me alone.
I can't calm down with you following me around.
I understand.
Come on, Kobato, let's go!
If we don't get a whole bunch of candy--
Oh, wow!
Hello!
Oh, it's just you, Kohaku.
Were you on a walk?
The weather's great today, isn't it?
What's with all this lollygagging!?
Is there something wrong with that?
Come on, Kohaku!
You're enough of a flake to get through, you tell her what's going on!
Tell Kobato?
Yeah! She's forgotten all about her wish, she's just flaking around lollygagging!
I haven't forgotten.
I know exactly what I wish for.
Of course you do.
What's Dobato up to?
Being a Dobato, obviously.
Are you mad, Ioryogi?
Damn straight I'm mad!
I'm mad, but I can't help it when she makes that face.
Kobato's made her choice.
What a fool.
There's a reason for everything.
So nothing is meaningless.
Is that how it works in Heaven?
Or does it apply us from the spirit world too?
It doesn't matter.
It's true for everyone.
I see.
Fujimoto!
Great, I found you.
Why?
Why are you so hung up on me?
What do you mean, why?
Do you just want to thank me?
You're barking up the wrong tree.
There's nothing you need to be grateful for.
You shouldn't expect anything more, either.
I care about you.
Of course I'm worried about someone I care about.
Plus, Sayaka told me to take care of you.
Whatever.
Isn't she important to you?
You can go see her anytime.
What are you on about?
You're just like Ioryogi sometimes.
You're both always mad about something.
Ioryogi's that stuffed animal you always haul around, right?
Yeah.
But he's really special!
We should get going.
You're right.
Kohaku.
You made your choice too, right?
Are you happy?
Yes.
How are you doing your laundry?
Drying it out must be really tough like that.
I can--
Fujimoto?
What?
I won't be able to spend tomorrow with you.
Good.
I'm finally free.
If you're happy about it, I'm happy too.
Take care.
Thank you.
I see.
This is so sudden.
Thanks for everything you've done for me. I'm sorry I can't say goodbye to Chiho and Chise.
I'm sure they'll miss you.
Have you talked with Sayaka yet?
I'm telling her next.
Okay.
It's already been a year since you moved in.
Yeah. Four seasons.
Spring, summer, fall, and winter.
They were all so fun.
Once you get settled in at your new place, get in touch.
Of course. As soon as I get settled in.
I've decided exactly what I wish for.
Hey, Dobato.
You know what that means, right?
Yes.
If you don't hurry up with the candy--
Don't you care what happens to yourself?
Are you an idiot?
I might be.
Yeah, you are.
A perfect 100 points on the idiot scale.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Ioryogi.
Have you said your goodbyes?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Okay.
Guess it's goodbye to here.
Is this really how you want to do it?
Look, the moon's so bright.
Yeah.
Hey, Kobato.
What, Ioryogi?
Are you sure you'll be happy just being by his side?
Who would I not be?
Just being with him is wonderful.
I thought she'd have told you.
No...
It must have been too hard for her to say.
Did she say where she was going?
No, just that she'd be in touch when she settled in.
He's gone.
Here he is.
Hold it!
Wait! She tried hard!
She may be stupid, may be clumsy, may be a flake.
She may be too positive and too honest for her own good.
But that's exactly how humans are supposed to be!
She's done great!
Please! You can't--
You can't just end her.
You know the Bunny can't do that, Ioryogi.
I'm sorry, Kobato.
Please don't apologize.
I've made up my mind.
I...
Thank you, Ioryogi.
What are you doing!?
Fujimoto...
Where are you going!?
I don't know.
Don't give me that!
Even in the end, you're angry.
Of course I am! You can't just disappear without saying anything!
I'm sorry.
Did I hurt your feelings?
No! That's not it!
Then why!?
Because of the contract.
Who's there?
I'm up here.
On top of her suitcase.
Yo.
It's Ioryogi.
But he's... a stuffed animal...
That's just what I pretend to be.
Anyway, about that contract.
Kobato. Show him.
Okay.
Hey...
What are you doing?
You're...
What's that!?
She's dead.
Kobato's soul doesn't belong to any world.
It wanders, attached to no life.
But thanks to a contract with someone higher up,
she had the chance to be reborn just one time and live life over.
Wait, what is this!?
But...
She was more worried about spending her time with you than fulfilling the contract.
Thus, the contract...
Was broken.
That's why I have to go away.
No way! Come on!
I was very happy when I was with you.
This is no good...
I wanted to say goodbye with a smile...
Wait!
Stop! Please!
Fujimoto...
You're the person I care the most about.
I always have.
And I always will.
Always.
Don't go!
Candy?
The candy...
It's filling up...
Kobato's wish has changed.
But the contract can't change.
She'll go to the place that she wanted to.
Fujimoto's candy...
It's so warm...
This isn't a gift, it's a curse!
Please! Let her be reborn in this world!
Dammit!
I'm sorry I can't do anything.
Don't apologize. I feel the same way.
I've been by her side the longest...
But I can't do anything.
But there's a reason for everything.
What's happening?
There's somewhere I must go.
Farewell.
In between the things I've lost
and the things I've been able to hold on to,
Your smile falls in that gap
It seems like I can reach it, but I can't
I can't fly
I just wanted to make you smile
My two wings weren't good enough
Why do I even have them?
Just smiling by your side
is all I can do.
Just warming you is good enough,
even though I want to embrace you
Even with these scarred, worthless wings,
right now I can smile
Next episode: "Tomorrow..."